

PERSONAL HİSTORY

I am Kutay Aygün, I am 19 years old, I am progressing in Computer Programming. I do research and develop projects to add value to myself in the field of web programming. I have a passion for robotic coding.

I want to transfer the knowledge, skills and work discipline I have gained throughout my education life to my business life and contribute to the goals of your company with the success I will achieve. I want to work in a dynamic environment where I can constantly improve myself.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- I made a smart home for the disabled with Arduino.
- I made a rocket for Teknofest.
- I made Corporate Sites.
- I made Blog Sites.
- I developed German Giant Projects.
- Received Entrepreneurship Certificates
- I won Search and Rescue Documents (IHH)

REACH ME

Phone Number: 0505 153 0477 E-Mail: kutayan870@gmail.com Web Address: www.kodgundem.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kutay-

ayg%C3%BCn/

Github: https://github.com/ckutaygun

İnstagram: @ckutaygun

KUTAY AYGÜN

-Software Developer -Laravel Dev.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Pineapple Production | Üsküdar/İstanbul | 10 Ağustos 2021-Aktif

- Team Leader
- Developing Laravel Projects
- Instructing the Team in Laravel
- Design and new versions of html template scripts
- Creating meaningful and proper code structure with backend.

Software Developer

Efekt Dijital | Ümraniye/İstanbul | 31Mayıs 2021- 1 Ağustos 2021

- -Developing Laravel Projects
- -Design and new versions of html template scripts
- Creating meaningful and proper code structure with backend.

Software Developer

IMECE YATIRIM A.Ş | Başakşehir/İstanbul | 11 Mart 2021-25 Mayıs 2021

- -In-house software development.
- -Back End Development

Software Developer

Kodgundem.com | Sakarya | 1 Haziran 2020- 26 Mayıs 2021

- -Kodgundem.com Kurucusu ve İçerik Üreticisi
- -Back End Development

Software Developer

Aquacentrum.de | Germany | 1 Nisan 2019- 17 Mayıs 2019

- -Making a water ions applicator
- -Back End Development

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Sakarya University of Applied Sciences

Computer programming

Hendek Anatolian High School

Graduate with Certificate of Achievement 2020

- -Head of the Hal Rocket Team
- -Hal Rocket Smart Home Project Leader

SKILLS

PHP, LARAVEL (Full), BOOSTRAP, JQUERY, AJAX, ARDUİNO ,HTML,JAVASCRIPT,VUE.JS, Socializing, Adaptation to Teamwork, Solving complex code structures